Curt Stern Papers 1907-1981 Mss.Ms.Coll.5
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence, 1907-1981 (Box 1-43)
  - Baltzer, Fritz, 1938-1964; 17 items (Box 2)
    Biographical and personal data; Biographical and personal data -- Boveri, Theodor; Congratulations, greetings, thanks; Dohrn, Anton; Drosophila genetics; Frisch, Karl von; Heitz, Emil; Invitations -- Switzerland; Lectures, public speaking -- Stern, Curt; Publication; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Balze, Felipe A. De La, 1961-1962; 6 items (Box 2)
  - Bancroft, I.A., 1966; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Baney, Robert M., 1972; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Bannerman, Robin M., 1970; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Barigozzi, C., 1972; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Barnes, Carole Wolff, 1971; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Barron, E. S. Guzman, 1944; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Barry, Patricia Z., 1969; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Barthelmess, A., 1952-1968; 6 items (Box 2)
  - Basden, E.B., 1970; 2 items (Box 2)
  - Basu, Sri Amit, 1964-1969; 17 items (Box 2)
  - Bateman, Angus J., 1957-1959; 6 items (Box 2)
  - Bauer, Hans, 1956; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Baur, Erwin, 1930-1933; 6 items (Box 2)
    Biographical and personal data; Genetics of plants -- Antirrhinum; International Congress of Genetics -- Fifth Congress; Publication
  - Bay Area Biologists Society, n.d.; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Bayreuther, Klaus, 1964; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Beach, Frank A., 1964; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Beadle, George Wells, 1946-1968; 2 folders (Box 2)
    Biographical and personal data; Biographical and personal data -- Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict; Biographical and personal data -- Wright, Sewall; California Institute of Technology; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Nobel Prize; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Origin of Genetics; Drosophila genetics -- Crossing over; Drosophila genetics -- Nomenclature; Drosophila genetics -- Suppressor-v; DuBridge, Lee Alvin; Editorial matters -- Genetics; Fellowships, assistantships; Goddard, David Rockwell; Hadorn, Ernst; Honors -- Kimber Award; Recommendations -- Kaplan; Recommendations -- Maas, Werner; Recommendations -- Stalker, Harrison Dailey; Requests for aid in finding positions; Stanford University; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry; University of California, Berkeley
    - Folder 1, 1955; 1 item (Box 2)
    - Folder 2, 1946-1968; 18 items (Box 2)
  - Beadle, Muriel (Mrs. George W.), 1968-1970; 3 items (Box 2)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ -- Chromosome abnormality and personality; Human genetics; Publication -- A Child's World; Zea (maize) genetics -- Beadle, George Wells
  - Beale, Geoffrey H., 1955; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Bearn, Alexander G., 1964-1975; 9 items (Box 2)
  - Beatty, R. Alan, 1973; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Becker, Gweneth Carson, 1960-1969; 9 items (Box 2)
    Biographical and personal data; Drosophila genetics; Graduate study; Radiation genetics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Becker, Hans Joachim, 1956-1975; 4 folders (Box 2)
    Biographical and personal data; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Genetic Mosaics; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Origin of Genetics; Cytogenetics; Delbruck, Max; Drosophila genetics; Embryology, developmental genetics; Eugenics; Goethe; History of biology, especially genetics; Munchen; Political issues -- Poland; Political issues -- West Germany; Recommendations -- Cooper, Kenneth Willard; Recommendations -- Seidel; Teaching
    - Folder 1, 1956-1961; 12 items (Box 2)
    - Folder 2, 1962-1967; 7 items (Box 2)
    - Folder 3, 1969-1971; 11 items (Box 2)
    - Folder 4, 1973-1975; 16 items (Box 2)
  - Beckman, Carolyn, 1971; 3 items (Box 2)
  - Beerman, Herman, 1964; 6 items (Box 2)
  - Beermann, W., 1961; 1 item (Box 2)
  - Belar, Gertrud, 1929-1956; 11 items (Box 3)
    Biographical and personal data; Kaiser-Wilhelm Institutes; Max-Planck Institutes; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Belar, Karl, 1925-1931; 3 folders (Box 3)
    Belar, Karl -- Death; Biographical and personal data; Cytogenetics; Editorial matters; Fellowships, assistantships -- John Innes Horticultural Institution; Fellowships, assistantships--California Institute of Technology; Kaiser-Wilhelm Institutes; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
    - Folder 1, 1925-1929; 8 items (Box 3)
    - Folder 2, 1929; 13 items (Box 3)
    - Folder 3, 1930-1931; 15 items (Box 3)
  - Bellido, A. Garcia, 1970; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Benda, Clemens E., 1960; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bender, Armin, 1941; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bender, Harvey A., 1965; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Benedek, Ladislaus, n.d.; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bengelsdorf, Irving S., 1965; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Benjamin, John D., 1966; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bennett, Charles, 1966; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bennett, John F., 1964; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bentley, David R., 1970; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Benzer, Seymour, 1967-1970; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Berg, Bea J. van den, 1974; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Berg, Raissa, 1975; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Berger, Charles A., 1943; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bergh, B.O., 1966-1973; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bergner, A. Dorothy, 1939-1964; 5 items (Box 3)
  - Bergsma, Daniel, 1966-1970; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Berkoff, Charles E., 1964; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bernier, Paul E., 1951; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bernstein, Felix, 1946-1949; 6 items (Box 3)
    Displaced German scholars; Graduate study -- Bernstein, Marianne Wiener; Human genetics; Requests for aid in finding positions; University of Rochester
  - Bernstein, Marianne E., 1949-1970; 23 items (Box 3)
    Displaced German scholars; Einstein, Albert; Goethe; Human genetics; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Berrill, John, 1940-1946; 6 items (Box 3)
  - Berry, George Packer, 1965; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bhasin, Mahinder Kumar, 1965-1969; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Bhattacharya, B., 1963-1967; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Bianchine, Josette, 1973; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bigelow, W.W., 1969; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Billingham, Rupert E., 1967; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Bingham, Woodbridge, 1964; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Biology equipment and supplies, 7 items (Box 3)
  - Biomedical Book Service, 1970; 2 items (Box 3)
  - BioScience (Journal), 1968; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bird, M. J., 1947; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Birdsell, Joseph B., 1950; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Birmingham, Lloyd and Marion, 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bishop, Sherman C., 1947-1948; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Blake, Igor R., 1971; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Blakeslee, Albert F., 1936-1948; 8 items (Box 3)
  - Blanc, Richard, 1952; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Blankenhorn, David H., 1968; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Bliven, Floyd, 1940-1942; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bluhm, Agnes, 1933; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Blum, Arnold F., 1946; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boas, Franz, 1939-1940; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Bodenstein, Dietrich, 19301946; 12 items (Box 3)
  - Bodmer, Walter, 1913; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Bogart, Ralph, 1974; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bohme, H., 1971; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Boklage, Charles E., 1975; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Boklage, Charles E. "The Embryogenesis of schizophrenia", n.d.; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boklage, Charles E. "Embryonic Determination...", 1974; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Born, James L., 1965; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boudo, Mrs. Stephen J., 1947; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bouman, H.D., 1947; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Boveri, Marcella, 1938; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boveri, Margaret, 1964; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boveri, Theodor (Box 3)
    Scope and Contents note
    see University of California Press
  - Bowen, Carroll G., 1968; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bowman, James T., 1969; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Box, Joan G., 1968; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Boyd, William C., 1949; 1 item (Box 3)
  - Boyes, J. Wallace, 1946-1971; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Brachet, Jean, 1947; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bragg, Desmond H., 1969; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Brasted, Adair (Box 3)
    see: Gould, Adair (Mrs. Charles
  - Braun, Warner, 1931-1947; 8 items (Box 3)
  - Braver, Gerald and Norma, 1966-1968; 4 items (Box 3)
  - Brehme, Katharine S., 1940-1944; 17 items (Box 3)
  - Brenton, Bill, 1970; 2 items (Box 3)
  - Bresch, Carsten, 1965-1972; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bresler, Jack B., 1967-1971; 3 items (Box 3)
  - Bridges, Calvin B., 1927-1938; 16 items (Box 4)
    Anderson, Ernest Gustav; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters -- Drosophila Information Service; Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Mohr, Otto Louis; Morgan, Thomas Hunt; Muller, Hermann Joseph; Publication; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Bridges, Philip N., 1946; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Brieger, Anneliese [Mrs. F.G.], 1937-1973; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Brieger, F.G., 1973; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Brink, R. Alexander, 1947-1966; 5 items (Box 4)
  - British Broadcasting Corp. Open University, 1975; 10 items (Box 4)
  - Bronk, Detlev W., 1967; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Brosseau, George E., Jr., 1959; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Brown, Edmund G. (Governor of California), 1961-1966; 4 items (Box 4)
  - Brown, Helen Lang, 1925; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Brown, Spencer, 1972; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Brown, W.M. Court, 1968; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Brownfield, E. Dorothy, 1964; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Browning, Luolin S., 1968; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Bucher, Thomas, 1963-1964; 6 items (Box 4)
  - Buck, John B., 1946-1975; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Bibliographical matters -- Genetics; Biographical and personal data; Evolution; Graduate study; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Political issues -- Loyalty oaths; Political issues--University of California, Berkeley; Radiation genetics; University of Rochester -- Charles, Donald Randolph; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1, 1946-1970; 16 items (Box 4)
    - Folder 2, 1975; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Buckless, Max, 1953; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Buice, Chris, 1970; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Bulgarian Academy of Sciences, 1951; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Bunche, Ralph J., 1960; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Buncher, Charles Ralph, 1965; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Burian, F., 1964; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Burkart, Arturo, 1933-1970; 5 items (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Charles H., 1954; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Burns, George W., 1969; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Burns, John M., 1967-1969; 4 items (Box 4)
  - Burton, Marie Rosenberg, 1942; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Buruga, Joseph, 1970; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Buser, Susanne, 1970; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Butler, E.G., 1945; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Butterfass, Theodor, 1967; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Butterfield, V.L., 1944; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Buyse, Adrian, 1941-1947; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Buzzati-Traverso, Adriano, 1935-1973; 4 items (Box 4)
  - Cahill, Ruth Mary. "Partial analysis of `Hybrid Sterility' within the species Drosophila Melanogaster", 1945; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Cairns, John, 1963-1964; 5 items (Box 4)
  - California. Committee on air pollution and radiation protection, 1958; 1 item (Box 4)
  - California. Department of Mental Hygiene, Langley Porter Neuropsychiatric Institute, 1958; 2 items (Box 4)
  - California. Department of Public Health, 1964; 2 items (Box 4)
  - California. Department of Social Welfare, 1960; 1 item (Box 4)
  - California Monthly. December 1981 Obituary, 2 items (Box 4)
  - California State Board of Health, 1964; 3 items (Box 4)
  - California. Study Commission on Mental Retardation 1964, 2 items (Box 4)
  - Calsoyas, C.D., 1966; 6 items (Box 4)
  - Cambridge University Press. Developmental and Cell Biology Series, 1975; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Campbell, Robert, 1957; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1971; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Cancro, Robert, 1969-1970; 5 items (Box 4)
  - Cantril, Simeon T., 1951-1954; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Carlson, Elof Axal, 1961-1972; 8 items (Box 4)
  - Carlson, J. Gordon, 1947; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Carmichael, L. (National Roster of Scientific Personnel), 1940; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Carson, Gweneth (See Becker, S.C., Becker, M.J.), 1956; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Carson, S.F., 1968; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Cartter, Allan M., 1965; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Carus, Frank E., 1970; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Casale, Anne, 1966; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm, 1946-1970; 2 folders (Box 4)
    Beadle, George Wells; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters; Genetics -- Ephestia; Publication; Radiation genetics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War II -- Hartmann, Max; World War II -- Kuhn, Alfred; Wright, Sewall
    - Folder 1, 1946-1947; 6 items (Box 4)
    - Folder 2, 1959-1970; 10 items (Box 4)
  - Caspersson, Torbjorn, 1945; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Castle, William E., 1947-1950; 5 items (Box 4)
  - Castleman, Kenneth R. "Pictorial output for computerized karyotyping", 1970; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Caullery, Maurice, 1933; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Cavalli-Sforza, Luigi L., 1966-1969; 4 items (Box 4)
  - Cell Biology: A Comprehensive Treatise, 1975; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Centeno, Judith Viegas, 1969; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Sciences, 1967; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Centerwall, Willard R., 1961-1972; 27 items (Box 4)
    Biographical and personal data; Graduate study; Human genetics -- India; Human genetics -- Y-chromosome; Publication
  - Cervenka, Jaroslav, 1964; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Chachere, Marvin L., 1970; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Chamberlain, Owen, 1968; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Chamberlin, Philip, 1964; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Chambers, Robert, 1945; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Chandra, Sharat, 1967; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Chao, Y.R., 1968; 3 items (Box 4)
  - Charles, Donald R., 1955; 1 item (Box 4)
  - Chaudhuri, Subhendu Datta, 1970; 2 items (Box 4)
  - Cheadle, Vernon I., 1964; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Chen, P.S., 1965; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Chen, Tao-Hsin, 1946; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Chiba, Sadako, 1966-1969; 17 items (Box 5)
  - Chicago, University of. Honorary Degree, 1973; 5 items (Box 5)
  - Chicago Cytogenetics Conference 1966, 4 folders (Box 5)
    Conferences and symposia; Cytogenetics; Human genetics; Publication; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
    - Folder 1, 1966; 3 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 2, 1966; 1 item (Box 5)
    - Folder 3, n.d.; 1 item (Box 5)
    - Folder 4, 1966; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Child, C.M., 1953; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Child Health and Development Studies, 1967; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Childs, Barton, 1961-1962; 6 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 1, n.d.; 1 item (Box 5)
    - Folder 2, n.d.; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Chown, Bruce, 1964; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Chu, Ernest H.Y., 1958-1972; 5 items (Box 5)
  - Citizens League Against the Sonic Boom, 1968; 3 items (Box 5)
  - City Commons Club (Berkeley, California), 1965; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Clarke, C.A., 1969; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Clausen, Lucy, 1945-1958; 4 items (Box 5)
  - Clausen, Roy, n.d.; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Clausen, Sam, n.d.; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Claxton, Jack H., 1965-1970; 20 items (Box 5)
    Biographical and personal data; Drosophila genetics; Embryology, developmental genetics; Fellowships, assistantships; Publication; Teaching -- University of New England (Australia); Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; University of California, Berkeley
  - Cleary, John Thomas, 1954; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Cleland, Ralph E., 1945-1967; 6 items (Box 5)
  - Close, Perry, 1972; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Cobb, W. Montague, 1957; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Cock, Alan G., 1954-1969; 9 items (Box 5)
  - Cockerell, T.D.A., 1944; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Cockrell, Robert A., 1965; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Coe, E.H., 1973; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Cohelan, Jeffery, 1970; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Cohen, Bernice, 1965-1966; 4 items (Box 5)
  - Cohen, I. Bernard, 1960-1965; 10 items (Box 5)
  - Cohen, Nathan W., 1965; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Cohen, Robert. Productions, 1963; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Coker, R. E., 1942; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Coleman, Richard W., 1967-1970; 9 items (Box 5)
  - Coleman, William, 1967-1971; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Collins, J.L., 1933; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Collins, Robert L., 1968; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Columbia University, 1943-1944; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Columbia University. Department of Biology, 1971; 1 item (Box 5)
  - Columbia University. Department of Zoology Newsletter, 1943-1946; 5 items (Box 5)
  - Combes, J.J., 1969; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Combs, Ernest F., 1972; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Comings, David E., 1970; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education in the Biological Sciences, 1966-1967; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Committee for Nuclear Responsibility, 1971-1972; 6 items (Box 5)
  - Committee on Developmental Biology, May 1952, 1 item (Box 5)
  - Los Compañeros, n.d.; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Comroe, Julius H., Jr., 1968; 2 items (Box 5)
  - Comstock, Ralph E., 1967-1968; 6 items (Box 5)
  - Conference on Genetic Disease Control 1970, 4 items (Box 5)
  - Conference on Human Genetics, Second International (Rome, 1961), 3 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Human Genetics -- Second Congress
  - Conference on Human Population Genetics in Israel 1961, 1972; 5 items (Box 5)
  - Conferences of Human Genetics, International, 1961; 6 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Human Genetics
  - Congress of Genetics, Sixth International (Ithaca, N.Y., 1932), 1931-1932; 3 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Genetics -- Sixth Congress
  - Congress of Genetics, Seventh International (U.S.S.R., 1937), 1936-1937; 6 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Genetics -- Seventh Congress
  - Congress of Genetics, Twelfth International (Tokyo, 1968), 1965-1968; 3 folders (Box 5)
    Committee activities; Congresses and symposia -- Japan; Embryology, developmental genetics; Genetics; International Congress of Genetics -- Twelfth Congress; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder 1, 1968; 12 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 2, 1967-1968; 19 items (Box 5)
    - Folder 3, 1965; 3 items (Box 5)
  - Congress of Genetics, Thirteenth International (Berkeley, 1973), 1972-1973; 18 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Genetics -- Thirteenth Congress
  - Congress of Human Genetics, Third International (Chicago, 1966), n.d.; 3 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Human Genetics -- Third Congress
  - Congresses of Genetics, International (1899-1968; summaries), 1965-1966; 9 items (Box 5)
    International Congress of Genetics
  - Conklin, Edwin Grant, 1951; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Conley, C. Lockard, 1959-1971; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Connell, Frank H., 1941; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Constance, Lincoln (Dean, College of Letters and Science, University of California, Berkeley) (Box 6)
    -see: University of California, Berkeley. Constance, Lincoln
  - Cook, Robert C., 1944; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Cooper, Jane G., 1967; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cooper, Kenneth W., 1939-1967; 5 folders (Box 6)
    Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data; Biographical and personal data -- Charles, Donald Randolph; California Institute of Technology; Columbia University -- Pollister, Arthur W.; Columbia University -- Schrader, Franz; Cytogenetics; Darlington, Cyril Dean; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters -- Genetics; Editorial matters -- Journal of American Zoology; Fellowships, assistantships; Holtfreter, Johannes; MacKnight, Robert H.; Monod, Jacques; Princeton University; Recommendations -- Blum, Harold; Recommendations -- Cooper, Kenneth Willard; Recommendations -- Mazia, Daniel; Recommendations -- Pollister, Arthur W.; Recommendations -- Poulson, Donald F.; Recommendations -- Sonneborn, Tracy M.; Recommendations -- Steinbach, H. Burr; Recommendations -- Tyler, Albert; Recommendations -- Wald, George; Referee's report -- Gregg, John; Schultz, Jack -- Chromosome pairing; University of Rochester; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1, 1939-1940; 7 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1941-1945; 23 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 3, 1946-1947; 18 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 4, 1948-1960; 18 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 5, 1962-1967; 20 items (Box 6)
  - Copeland, Gene, 1 item (Box 6)
  - Cordeiro, Antonio R., 1959; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Corner, George Washington, 1941-1958; 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Folder 1, 1941-1944; 11 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1949-1958; 5 items (Box 6)
  - Correns, Anna Eva, 1965; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Correns, Carl, 1924; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Cossey, Mr. and Mrs. Allen, 1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Counce, Sheila, 1972; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cox, Gertrude M., 1966; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Crackpot letters, 1951-1976 (ca); 36 items (Box 6)
  - Crandoll, Barbara F., 1971; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cranston, Alan, 1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Creighton, Harriet, 1942; 9 items (Box 6)
  - Crew, F.A.E., 1939; 6 items (Box 6)
  - Cross, Ira B., 1971; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Crouse, Helen V., 1947-1968; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Crow, James F., 1962-1971; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Crowley, Clement R., 1952; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Csik, L., 1958; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Cundy, Kenneth R., 1964; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cutting, Windsor, 1964; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Cytogenetics (Journal), 1961-1966; 18 items (Box 6)
  - Czechoslovak Medical Society, 1962-1963; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Daedalus (Journal), 1970; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Dahlberg, Gunnar (Box 6)
  - Dalton, Clark, 1946; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Danforth, C.H., 1935-1951; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Daniels, John, 1968; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Danner, Helen, 1965; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Darley, C. Barrington, 1947-1948; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Darlington, Cyril D., 1932-1946; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Daske, Yves, 1967; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Datta, Rajat Kumar, 1969-1970; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Davenport, Charles B., 1933-1942; 4 items (Box 6)
  - Davidenkova, Eugenia, n.d.; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1965; 3 items (Box 6)
  - Davis, Betty, 1969; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Davis, Bradley M., 1948; 1 item (Box 6)
  - Davis, Watson, 1962; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Day, Robert Winsor, 1963-1972; 1 item (Box 6)
  - DeBeer, Sir Gavin, 1960-1972; 4 items (Box 6)
  - DeFrank, Josephine, 1947; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Degenhardt, Karl-Heinz, 1961-1972; 7 items (Box 6)
  - Deignan, Mrs. Ormand, 1947; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Delbrück, Max, 1938-1968; 13 items (Box 6)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biographical and personal data; California Institute of Technology; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Kimber Award; Frisch, Karl von; Genetics; Goldschmidt, Richard Benedict; Haldane, John Burdon Sanderson; Invitations; Morgan, Thomas Hunt; Political issues; Recommendations -- Becker, Hans Joachim; Recommendations -- Ursprung, Heinrich; University of California, Berkeley; University of Koln -- Institute of Genetics
  - Demerec, Mary, 1966; 2 items (Box 6)
  - Demerec, Milislav, 1933-1947; 7 folders (Box 6)
    Biographical and personal data; Brasted, Adair; Brehme, Catherine; Bridges, Calvin B.; Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm; Charles, Donald Randolph; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia -- Cold Spring Harbor Symposium; Cytogenetics; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Drosophila Information Service; Editorial matters -- Advances in Genetics; Ephrussi, Boris; Evolution; Fano, Ugo; Genetics of plants -- Delphinium; Hoover, Margaret; International Congress of Genetics; International Union of Biological Societies; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole -- Gene Conferences; Neel, James V.; Political issues; Publication; Publication -- Biology of Drosophila; Schultz, Jack; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Stalker, Harrison Dailey; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1, 1933-1935; 25 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 2, 1936-1937; 12 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 3, 1938-1939; 22 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 4, 1940-1941; 22 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 5, 1942-1943; 10 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 6, 1944-1945; 29 items (Box 6)
    - Folder 7, 1946-1947; 20 items (Box 6)
  - Dempster, Everett Ross, 1946-1970; 2 folders (Box 7)
    Biographical and personal data; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters; Evolution; Human genetics; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Mathematics; Political issues; University of California, Berkeley
    - Folder 1, 1946-1966; 13 items (Box 7)
    - Folder 2, 1966-1970; 12 items (Box 7)
  - Denell, Robert, 1972; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Dennes, William R., 1961; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Dermen, Haig, 1955; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Descartes, Blanche, n.d.; 1 item (Box 7)